[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Hey, everyone.
嘿大家。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this episode, we're going to do something special,
在这一集中，我们将做一些特别的事情，
and that's write our own classifier from scratch.
那是从头开始编写我们自己的分类器。
If you're new to machine learning,
如果你是机器学习的新手，
this is a big milestone.
这是一个重要的里程碑。
Because if you can follow along and do this on your own,
因为如果你可以自己跟随并做到这一点，
it means you understand an important piece of the puzzle.
这意味着你理解了这个难题的一个重要部分。
The classifier we're going to write today
我们今天要写的分类器
is a scrappy version of k-Nearest Neighbors.
是k-Nearest Neighbors的杂乱版本。
That's one of the simplest classifiers around.
这是最简单的分类器之一。
First, here's a quick outline of what we'll do in this episode.
首先，这里简要介绍一下我们将在本集中做些什么。
We'll start with our code from Episode 4, Let's
我们将从第4集“Let”中的代码开始
Write a Pipeline.
写一个管道。
Recall in that episode we did a simple experiment.
回想一下那集我们做了一个简单的实验。
We imported a data set and split it into train and test.
我们导入了一个数据集并将其拆分为训练和测试。
We used train to train a classifier,
我们用火车来训练分类器，
and test to see how accurate it was.
并测试它是多么准确。
Writing the classifier is the part
编写分类器就是其中的一部分
we're going to focus on today.
我们今天要专注于今天。
Previously we imported the classifier
以前我们导入了分类器
from a library using these two lines.
来自使用这两行的图书馆。
Here we'll comment them out and write our own.
在这里，我们将评论它们并编写我们自己的。
The rest of the pipeline will stay exactly the same.
管道的其余部分将保持完全相同。
I'll pop in and out of the screencast to explain things
我会弹出进出截屏视频来解释一些事情
as we go along.
我们一起去。
To start, let's run our pipeline to remind ourselves
首先，让我们运行我们的管道来提醒自己
what the accuracy was.
准确度是多少。
As you can see, it's over 90%.
如你所见，它超过90％。
And that's the goal for the classifier
这就是分类器的目标
we'll write ourselves.
我们会自己写。
Now let's comment out that import.
现在让我们注释掉那个导入。
Right off the bat, this breaks our code.
蝙蝠，这打破了我们的代码。
So the first thing we need to do is fix our pipeline.
所以我们需要做的第一件事是修复我们的管道。
And to do that, we'll implement a class for our classifier.
为此，我们将为分类器实现一个类。
I'll call it ScrappyKNN.
我称之为ScrappyKNN。
And by scrappy, I mean bare bones.
通过斗志，我的意思是裸骨。
Just enough to get it working.
足以让它运作起来。
Next, I'll change our pipeline to use it.
接下来，我将更改我们的管道以使用它。
Now let's see what methods we need to implement.
现在让我们看看我们需要实现哪些方法。
Looking at the interface for a classifier,
查看分类器的界面，
we see there are two we care about-- fit,
我们看到有两个我们在乎 - 合身，
which does the training, and predict,
进行训练并预测，
which does the prediction.
做预测。
First we'll declare our fit method.
首先，我们将声明我们的拟合方法。
Remember this takes the features and labels for the training set
请记住，这会获取训练集的功能和标签
as input, so we'll add parameters for those.
作为输入，我们将为这些添加参数。
Now let's move on to our predict method.
现在让我们继续我们的预测方法。
As input, this receives the features for our testing data.
作为输入，它接收我们的测试数据的功能。
And as output, it returns predictions for the labels.
作为输出，它返回标签的预测。
Our first goal is to get the pipeline working,
我们的第一个目标是让管道工作，
and to understand what these methods do.
并了解这些方法的作用。
So before we write our real classifier,
所以在我们编写真正的分类器之前，
we'll start with something simpler.
我们将从更简单的事情开始。
We'll write a random classifier.
我们将编写一个随机分类器。
And by random, I mean we'll just guess the label.
随机，我的意思是我们只是猜测标签。
To start, we'll add some code to the fit and predict methods.
首先，我们将为拟合和预测方法添加一些代码。
In fit, I'll store the training data in this class.
在拟合中，我会将训练数据存储在此课程中。
You can think of this as just memorizing it.
你可以把它想象成只是记住它。
And you'll see why we do that later on.
你会明白为什么我们以后会这样做。
Inside the predict method, remember
在预测方法中，请记住
that we'll need to return a list of predictions.
我们需要返回一个预测列表。
That's because the parameter, X_test, is actually
那是因为参数X_test实际上是
a 2D array, or list of lists.
2D数组或列表列表。
Each row contains the features for one testing example.
每行包含一个测试示例的功能。
To make a prediction for each row,
要对每一行进行预测，
I'll just randomly pick a label from the training data
我只是从训练数据中随机选择一个标签
and append that to our predictions.
并将其附加到我们的预测中。
At this point, our pipeline is working again.
在这一点上，我们的管道再次运作。
So let's run it and see how well it does.
所以，让我们运行它，看看它有多好。
Recall there are three different types of flowers
回想一下有三种不同类型的花
in the iris dataset, so accuracy should be about 33%.
在虹膜数据集中，精度应该在33％左右。
Now we know the interface for a classifier.
现在我们知道了分类器的接口。
But when we started this exercise,
但是当我们开始这个练习时，
our accuracy was above 90%.
我们的准确率超过90％。
So let's see if we can do better.
那么让我们看看我们是否可以做得更好。
To do that, we'll implement our classifier,
为此，我们将实现我们的分类器，
which is based on k-Nearest Neighbors.
这基于k-Nearest Neighbors。
Here's the intuition for how that algorithm works.
这是该算法如何工作的直觉。
Let's return to our drawings of green dots and red dots
让我们回到我们的绿点和红点图纸
from the last episode.
从上一集开始。
Imagine the dots we see on the screen
想象一下我们在屏幕上看到的点
are the training data we memorized in the fit method,
是我们在拟合方法中记忆的训练数据，
say for a toy dataset.
对于玩具数据集说。
Now imagine we're asked to make a prediction for this testing
现在假设我们被要求对此测试做出预测
point that I'll draw here in gray.
我将在这里用灰色画出来。
How can we do that?
我们怎么能这样做？
Well in a nearest neighbor classifier,
那么在最近邻分类器中，
it works exactly like it sounds.
它听起来就像听起来一样。
We'll find the training point that's
我们会找到训练点
closest to the testing point.
最接近测试点。
This point is the nearest neighbor.
这一点是最近的邻居。
Then we'll predict that the testing
然后我们会预测测试
point has the same label.
point有相同的标签。
For example, we'll guess that this testing dot is green,
例如，我们猜测这个测试点是绿色的，
because that's the color of its nearest neighbor.
因为那是它最近邻居的颜色。
As another example, if we had a testing dot over here,
再举一个例子，如果我们在这里有一个测试点，
we'd guess that it's red.
我们猜它是红色的。
Now what about this one right in the middle?
那么这个正好在中间呢？
Imagine that this dot is equidistant to the nearest
想象一下，这个点与最近的点等距离
green dot and the nearest red one.
绿点和最近的红点。
There's a tie, so how could we classify it?
有一个平局，所以我们怎么能分类呢？
Well one way is we could randomly break the tie.
那么一种方法是我们可以随机打破平局。
But there's another way, and that's where k comes in.
但还有另一种方式，那就是k进来的地方。
K is the number of neighbors we consider
K是我们考虑的邻居数量
when making our prediction.
在做出预测时。
If k was 1, we'd just look at the closest training point.
如果k为1，我们只看最近的训练点。
But if k was 3, we'd look at the three closest.
但如果k为3，我们会看三个最接近的。
In this case, two of those are green and one is red.
在这种情况下，其中两个是绿色，一个是红色。
To predict, we could vote and predict the majority class.
为了预测，我们可以投票和预测大多数班级。
Now there's more detail to this algorithm,
现在有更详细的算法，
but that's enough to get us started.
但这足以让我们开始。
To code this up, first we'll need a way
要对此进行编码，首先我们需要一种方法
to find the nearest neighbor.
找到最近的邻居。
And to do that, we'll measure the straight line
要做到这一点，我们将衡量直线
distance between two points, just like you do with a ruler.
两点之间的距离，就像你用尺子做的那样。
There's a formula for that called the Euclidean Distance,
有一个称为欧氏距离的公式，
and here's what the formula looks like.
这是公式的样子。
It measures the distance between two points,
它测量两点之间的距离，
and it works a bit like the Pythagorean Theorem.
它有点像毕达哥拉斯定理。
A squared plus B squared equals C squared.
平方加B平方等于C平方。
You can think of this term as A, or the difference
您可以将此术语视为A或差异
between the first two features.
介于前两个功能之间。
Likewise, you can think of this term as B,
同样，您可以将此术语视为B，
or the difference between the second pair of features.
或者第二对特征之间的区别。
And the distance we compute is the length of the hypotenuse.
我们计算的距离是斜边的长度。
Now here's something cool.
现在这里很酷。
Right now we're computing distance
现在我们正在计算距离
in two-dimensional space, because we have just two
在二维空间，因为我们只有两个
features in our toy dataset.
我们的玩具数据集中的功能。
But what if we had three features or three dimensions?
但是，如果我们有三个特征或三个维度呢？
Well then we'd be in a cube.
那么我们就在一个立方体中。
We can still visualize how to measure distance
我们仍然可以想象如何测量距离
in the space with a ruler.
在带有尺子的空间里。
But what if we had four features or four dimensions,
但是，如果我们有四个特征或四个维度，
like we do in iris?
就像我们在虹膜中做的那样？
Well, now we're in a hypercube, and we
好吧，现在我们在一个超立方体中，我们
can't visualize this very easy.
无法想象这很容易。
The good news is the Euclidean Distance
好消息是欧几里德距离
works the same way regardless of the number of dimensions.
无论维数多少，都以相同的方式工作。
With more features, we can just add more terms to the equation.
通过更多功能，我们可以在等式中添加更多术语。
You can find more details about this online.
您可以在线找到更多相关信息。
Now let's code up Euclidean distance.
现在让我们编码欧几里德距离。
There are plenty of ways to do that,
有很多方法可以做到这一点，
but we'll use a library called scipy that's
但我们将使用一个名为scipy的库
already installed by Anaconda.
已经由Anaconda安装。
Here, A and B are lists of numeric features.
这里，A和B是数字特征的列表。
Say A is a point from our training data,
说A是我们的训练数据中的一点，
and B is a point from our testing data.
和B是我们测试数据的一点。
This function returns the distance between them.
此函数返回它们之间的距离。
That's all the math we need, so now
这就是我们需要的所有数学，所以现在
let's take a look at the algorithm for a classifier.
让我们来看看分类器的算法。
To make a prediction for a test point,
要对测试点进行预测，
we'll calculate the distance to all the training points.
我们将计算到所有训练点的距离。
Then we'll predict the testing point has the same label
然后我们预测测试点具有相同的标签
as the closest one.
作为最接近的一个。
I'll delete the random prediction we made,
我会删除我们做的随机预测，
and replace it with a method that finds the closest training
并用找到最接近的训练的方法替换它
point to the test point.
指向测试点。
For this video hard, I'll hard-code k to 1,
对于这个视频很难，我会​​硬编码k到1，
so we're writing a nearest neighbor classifier.
所以我们正在写一个最近邻分类器。
The k variable won't appear in our code,
k变量不会出现在我们的代码中，
since we'll always just find the closest point.
因为我们总能找到最接近的点。
Inside this method, we'll loop over all the training points
在这种方法中，我们将遍历所有训练点
and keep track of the closest one so far.
并记录到目前为止最接近的一个。
Remember that we memorized the training data in our fit
请记住，我们记住了训练数据
function, and X_train contains the features.
函数，X_train包含这些功能。
To start, I'll calculate the distance from the test point
首先，我将计算距测试点的距离
to the first training point.
到第一个训练点。
I'll use this variable to keep track of the shortest
我将使用此变量来跟踪最短的变量
distance we've found so far.
到目前为止我们找到的距离。
And I'll use this variable to keep
我将使用此变量来保持
track of the index of the training point that's closest.
跟踪最接近的训练点的索引。
We'll need this later to retrieve its label.
我们稍后需要它来检索它的标签。
Now we'll iterate over all the other training points.
现在我们将迭代所有其他训练点。
And every time we find a closer one,
每当我们找到一个更接近的，
we'll update our variables.
我们将更新我们的变量。
Finally, we'll use the index to return
最后，我们将使用索引返回
the label for the closest training example.
最接近的训练样例的标签。
At this point, we have a working nearest neighbor classifier,
此时，我们有一个工作的最近邻分类器，
so let's run it and see what the accuracy is.
所以让我们运行它，看看准确性是多少。
As you can see, it's over 90%.
如你所见，它超过90％。
And we did it.
我们做到了。
When you run this on your own, the accuracy
当你自己运行时，准确性
might be a bit different because of randomness in the train test
由于列车测试中的随机性，可能会有点不同
split.
分裂。
Now if you can code this up and understand it,
现在，如果您可以编写并理解它，
that's a big accomplishment because it
这是一个很大的成就，因为它
means you can write a simple classifier from scratch.
意味着你可以从头开始编写一个简单的分类器。
Now, there are a number of pros and cons
现在，有一些优点和缺点
to this algorithm, many of which you can find online.
对于这个算法，你可以在网上找到很多。
The basic pro is that it's relatively easy to understand,
理解的基本原则是相对容易理解，
and works reasonably well for some problems.
并且在某些问题上工作得相当好。
And the basic cons are that it's slow,
而基本的缺点是它很慢，
because it has to iterate over every training point
因为它必须迭代每个训练点
to make a prediction.
做出预测。
And importantly, as we saw in Episode 3,
而且重要的是，正如我们在第3集中所看到的，
some features are more informative than others.
某些功能比其他功能更丰富。
But there's not an easy way to represent
但是没有一种简单的表达方式
that in k-Nearest Neighbors.
在k-最近邻居。
In the long run, we want a classifier
从长远来看，我们需要一个分类器
that learns more complex relationships between features
学习功能之间更复杂的关系
and the label we're trying to predict.
以及我们试图预测的标签。
A decision tree is a good example of that.
决策树就是一个很好的例子。
And a neural network like we saw in TensorFlow Playground
和我们在TensorFlow Playground中看到的神经网络一样
is even better.
甚至更好。
OK, hope that was helpful.
好的，希望这很有帮助。
Thanks as always for watching.
一如既往地感谢您的收看。
You can follow me on Twitter for updates and, of course,
您可以在Twitter上关注我的更新，当然，
Google Developers.
Google Developers。
And I'll see you guys next time.
我下次会见到你们。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]